Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - Subseries H: South Africa grant files, 1980-2014
    - Centre for Education Policy Development (CEPD), 1996-2014; Centre for Education Policy Development (Johannesburg, South Africa)
      - #8665, #7932 (#99-137), #7572 (#97-99), #8058 (#00-74).Â Alex Boraine, 1997-2001 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - #8803. South African University Vice Chancellor's Association research capacity, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - #8803. SAUVCA (South African University Vice Chancellor's Association) research projects, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - #8922. SAUVCA (South African University Vice Chancellor's Association): Establishment of a management capacity development unit, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - #8922. Management support, 2000-2006 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - #9535. Equity development tracking study, 2001-2004 (Box 30, Folder 14-15)
      - #9535. Equity development tracking study. SSC, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
      - #9535. Equity development tracking study, 2001-2002 (Box 169, Folder 11)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/10
      - #10565. Seed funding: SA International Festival of Books, 2002 (Box 169, Folder 12)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/10/2
      - #10565. South Africa Bookfest, 2002-2004 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - #10875. Mandlovu Development Institute planning grant, 2002, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - #10875. Mandlovu Development Institute planning grant, 2001-2003 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - #11037. South African Institute for Advancement, 2002-2008 (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
        Inyathelo - South African Institute for Advancement
      - #11307. SA Institute for Advancement, 2003-2007 (Box 169, Folder 13)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/2/10/5
      - #11038. The Nonprofit Partnership, 2001-2002, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 23)
        Non Profit Partnership (South Africa)
      - #11038. The Nonprofit Partnership, 2002, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - #11038. Nonprofit consortium, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - #11038. Nonprofit Partnership, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 26-27)
      - #11973. AP/IBIS. Core support funding to provincial NGO coalitions, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - #11973. SANGOCO core support, 2003-2007 (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
      - #13494. South African farm life dissemination and communication project, 2004-2006 (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
      - #13500. Constitution Hill project, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        Constitution Hill (Heritage complex: Johannesburg, South Africa)
        Race and Intergroup Relations, Cultural Awareness
      - #13500. Constitution Hill project, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - #13731. Paper addressing the law and social transformation. Sabbatical: Geoff Budlender, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 8)
        Budlender, Geoff
      - #13731. Paper addressing the law and social transformation. Sabbatical: Geoff Budlender, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - #13761. Centre for Education Policy Development, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - #13761. Ex-combatant base-line data study, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - #14179. The farm life in South Africa project, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - #14179. Farm life in South Africa project, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - #14303. PILCH- Public Interest Law Clearing House. R-Poor (rural poor), 2004-2010 (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
      - #14305. Atlantic Integrated Refugee Rights Project, 2006-2009 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - #14305. Integrated refugee rights program. Ref-Mig. (refugees and migrants) 1, 2006-2010 (Box 31, Folder 17-20)
      - #14305. Integrated refugee rights program. Ref-Mig. (refugees and migrants) 2, 2003-2009 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
      - #14957. Alliance of Land and Rural Movements (ALARM), 2006-2008 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
        Environmental Justice
      - #14958. Farm life project: phase 2. R-Poor (rural poor), 2006-2008 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
      - #14958. Farm life project: phase 2, 2006-2008 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - #15068. Technical assistance to the National Department of Health, 1998, 2004, 2007-2012 (Box 32, Folder 9-12)
        South Africa. Department of Health
        Nursing
      - #15211. 6th Annual Congress of Midwives Society, 2006-2007 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        Reproductive Health
        Medical Specialties
      - #15558. Gay and lesbian service delivery cluster, 2007-2011 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
      - #15866. Transgender and intersex advocacy cluster, 2007-2009 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - #15866. Transgender and inter-sex advocacy cluster, 2007, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - #16164. Gay and lesbian special delivery cluster (2): FEW (Forum for the Empowerment of Women), DLGCHC (Durban Lesbian and Gay Community and Health Centre), 2008, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        Forum for the Empowerment of Women
        Durban Lesbian and Gay Community and Health Centre
      - #16164. Service delivery cluster (2). Advocate for the provision of high quality health and other services to the gay and lesbian community by supporting two key regional organizations, 2008; Forum for the Empowerment of Women; Durban Lesbian and Gay Community and Health Centre (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - #16483. Lesbian and gay cluster bridging fund, 2006-2008; Out in Africa (Film festival); Behind the Mask (Box 33, Folder 8)
        Out in Africa (Film festival)
      - #16483. Gay and lesbian media and culture cluster bridging funds, 2007-2008; Out in Africa (Film festival); Behind the Mask (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - #16484. Gay and lesbian culture and media cluster, 2008; Out in Africa (Film festival); Behind the Mask; Gay and Lesbian Archives of South Africa (Box 33, Folder 10)
        Gay and Lesbian Archives of South Africa
      - #16484. LGBTI media cluster: Out in Africa, 2006-2009; Out in Africa (Film festival); Behind the Mask; Gay and Lesbian Archives of South Africa (Box 33, Folder 11-12)
        - Behind the Mask (BTM) 2005 annual report, 2006; CD-5256; Behind the Mask (Box 33, Folder 11)
          Duplicate of disc in box 28, folder 7.
      - #16484. Out in Africa. Lesbian and gay media cluster. LGBTI. I, 2007-2010; Out in Africa (Film festival); Behind the Mask; Gay and Lesbian Archives of South Africa (Box 33, Folder 13-15)
      - #16484. Out in Africa. Lesbian and gay media cluster. LGBTI. II, 2007-2008, 2010; Out in Africa (Film festival); Behind the Mask; Gay and Lesbian Archives of South Africa (Box 33, Folder 16-17)
      - #16577. Atlantic archival cluster: key films, Archival Platform, Historical Papers, SAHA (South African History Archives), 2008-2009; South African History Archives; University of the Witwatersrand. Library. Historical Papers; University of Cape Town. Department of Social Anthropology. Archival Platform (Box 33, Folder 18)
        South African History Archives
        University of the Witwatersrand. Library. Historical Papers
        University of Cape Town. Department of Social Anthropology. Archival Platform
      - #16577. Atlantic archival cluster, 2008; South African History Archives; University of the Witwatersrand. Library. Historical Papers; University of Cape Town. Department of Social Anthropology. Archival Platform (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - #16857. Fellowship for Nathan Geffen (TAC (Treatment Action Campaign)) and Jonathan Berger (ALP (AIDS Law Project)), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 20)
        Geffen, Nathan
        Berger, Jonathan (Lawyer)
        AIDS Law Project (University of the Witwatersrand)
        Treatment Action Campaign
      - #16857. Fellowship for Nathan Geffen (TAC) and Jonathan Berger (ALP), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - #16908. FUNDISA (Forum of University Nursing Deans of South Africa) planning grant, 2008-2009 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        Forum of University Nursing Deans of South Africa
        Population Health Educational Management
      - #16908. To support FUNDISA (Forum of University Nursing Deans of South Africa) with a planning grant in the development of a legal entity, 2008-2009 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - #16961. Organizational capacity development South Africa, 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - #17385. Atlantic archival cluster, 2008-2011; South African History Archives; University of the Witwatersrand. Library. Historical Papers; University of Cape Town. Department of Social Anthropology. Archival Platform; University of Cape Town. Visual History Archive (Box 34, Folder 4-6)
        University of Cape Town. Visual History Archive
        Delvering on Democracy
      - #17664. FUNDISA (Forum of University Nursing Deans of South Africa). UNEDSA grant coordination and management, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - #17664. UNEDSA grant coordination and management, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - #17738. LGBTI cluster 2: FEW, the Inner Circle, DLGCHC, Inclusive and Affirmative Ministries, 2009-2012; Forum for the Empowerment of Women; Durban Lesbian and Gay Community and Health Centre; Inner Circle (Organization); Inclusive and Affirmative Ministries (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
        Inner Circle (Organization)
        Inclusive and Affirmative Ministries
      - #18777. Integrated refugee rights program (2), 2006, 2008-2013 (Box 34, Folder 11-12)
      - #18780. Production of 3 documentary films, 2010-2012 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - #18780. What does it mean to be South African? Exploring identity, citizenship, and nationhood in the new South Africa, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - #18894. South Africa Executive Leadership Education in Health. SAELPH, 2012-2013 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - #19122. Constitutional advocacy cluster grant: Section 27, Equal Education, Social Justice Coalition, Socio-Economic Rights Institute. Dem-Con (democracy-constitution), 2009-2013; SECTION27 (Braamfontein, South Africa); Equal Education (Nonprofit organisation); Social Justice Coalition (South Africa); Socio-Economic Rights Institute of South Africa (Box 34, Folder 16-18)
        SECTION27 (Braamfontein, South Africa)
        Equal Education (Nonprofit organisation)
        Social Justice Coalition (South Africa)
        Socio-Economic Rights Institute of South Africa
      - #19122. Equal Education 2009 Annual Report, 2010; Equal Education (Nonprofit organisation) (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - #19123. Rural poverty cluster: LRC, RLT, Probono.org, Black Sash, Inyathelo, CALS, 2009-2012; Legal Resources Centre (South Africa); Rural League Trust; Black Sash (Society). Trust; Inyathelo - South African Institute for Advancement; University of the Witwatersrand. Centre for Applied Legal Studies (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
        Legal Resources Centre (South Africa)
        Rural League Trust
        University of the Witwatersrand. Centre for Applied Legal Studies
      - #19124. LGBTI advocacy and sustainability cluster: Gender Dynamix, Intersex SA, the Inner Circle, Hivos, Strategy and Tactics, 2009-2011; Gender Dynamix; Intersex South Africa; Inner Circle (Organization); HIVOS (Organization). Regional Office for Southern Africa; S and T (Firm) (Box 35, Folder 3)
        Gender Dynamix
        Intersex South Africa
        HIVOS (Organization). Regional Office for Southern Africa
        S and T (Firm)
      - #19124. LGBTI advocacy and sustainability, 2010; Gender Dynamix; Intersex South Africa; Inner Circle (Organization); HIVOS (Organization). Regional Office for Southern Africa; S and T (Firm) (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - #19271. Constitution advocacy cluster: Section 27, 2007-2013; SECTION27 (Braamfontein, South Africa); Equal Education (Nonprofit organisation); Socio-Economic Rights Institute of South Africa (Box 35, Folder 5-7)
      - #19420. Dissemination of xeno study findings, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - #19420. Dissemination of the findings and recommendations of the study on South African Civil Society and Xenophobia, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - #20006. Rural poverty cluster: BRC, LRC, PLAAS, CALS, SCAT, RULAC, MAGI, Inyathelo, 2001, 2009-2013; Border Rural Committee; Legal Resources Centre (South Africa); University of the Western Cape. Programme for Land and Agrarian Studies; University of the Witwatersrand. Centre for Applied Legal Studies; Social Change Assistance Trust; Rhodes University Law Clinic; Multi Agency Grants Initiative; Inyathelo - South African Institute for Advancement (Box 35, Folder 10-12)
        University of the Western Cape. Programme for Land and Agrarian Studies
        Social Change Assistance Trust
        Rhodes University Law Clinic
        Multi Agency Grants Initiative
      - #20204. Country-focused strategic learning and grantee consultative forums and convenings, 2010-2014 (Box 35, Folder 13)
        Legacy Program Area
      - #20286. National nursing summit, 2008-2012 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - #20286. National nursing summit, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - #20633. FUNDISA (Forum of University Nursing Deans of South Africa) (UNEDSA Project Management Services), 2011, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - #21266. Advice office and public interest law cluster: Black Sash, CCJD, LRC, ProBono.org, RLT, 2010-2013; Black Sash (Society). Trust; Centre for Community Justice and Development; Legal Resources Centre (South Africa); Rural Legal Trust (Box 35, Folder 17-19)
        Centre for Community Justice and Development
        Rural Legal Trust
      - #21267. Democracy and constitionalism cluster: CASAC, Equal Ed, HIVOS, Section 27, SER, SJC, 2008, 2010-2014; Council for the Advancement of the South African Constitution; Equal Education (Nonprofit organisation); HIVOS (Organization). Regional Office for Southern Africa; SECTION27 (Braamfontein, South Africa); Socio-Economic Rights Institute of South Africa; Social Justice Coalition (South Africa) (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
        Council for the Advancement of the South African Constitution
    - Centre for Health Policy, 2008-2010
      Centre for Health Policy
      - #15962. Nursing policy development and practice research, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - #15962. Policy and operational research on nursing, 2008-2010 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Centre for Human Rights, 1995-2004; University of Pretoria. Centre for Human Rights
      University of Pretoria. Centre for Human Rights
      - #96-79 andÂ #7521Â (#97-48). Integrated Bar Project, 1995-2000 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
      - #7521, #7839, #7454. Integrated Bar Project, 1996-2000 (Box 169, Folder 14-15)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab.1, Dr.3B, 37/3/1/5
      - #7521 (#97-48); #8021 (#00-44). Integrated Bar Project, 2000-2002, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - #8021. IBP (Integrated Bar Project)- 2000 gift, 1999, 200-2001 (Box 169, Folder 16)
        Dublin cabinet file, Cab. 1, Dr. 3B, 37/3/1/5/1
    - Centre for Non-Profit Studies, 2000-2001
      - Centre for Non-Profit Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
    - Centre for Policy Studies, 1999-2002; Centre for Policy Studies (Johannesburg, South Africa)
      Centre for Policy Studies (Johannesburg, South Africa)
      - #7941 (T99-146). Research project. #8908. Workshop on the impact of foreign donor funding, 1999, 2001 (Box 169, Folder 17)
        Dublin cabinet file, Cab. 1, Dr. 4B, 37/4/7
      - #7941 (#99-146). Research project. Civil Society study, 1999-2002 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - #8908. Â Workshop on the impact of foreign donor funding, 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Centre for Rural Health, 2005-2008; University of KwaZulu-Natal
      Centre for Rural Health
      - #13918. Strengthening human resources in health in rural KwaZulu Natal. learning clusters project, 2005-2006 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - #13918. Strengthening HR in rural KZN, 2005-2007 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - #16653. Rural-based health training, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - #16653. To strengthen rural-based health training, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Centre for the Study of Violence and Reconciliation (CSVR), 1999-2013; Centre for the Study of Violence and Reconciliation
      Centre for the Study of Violence and Reconciliation
      - General materials, 2003, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - General materials, 2004-2005 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - #9456. Apartheid Museum feasibility study, 1999-2002 (Box 36, Folder 20)
        History Museums
      - #9456. Apartheid museum I, 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 21-23)
        - Constitution Hill: Invest Now!, CD-5260; Johannesburg Development Agency (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - Constitution Hill: Invest Now!, CD-5260; Johannesburg Development Agency (Box 36, Folder 23)
        - Constitution Hill - Johannesburg--proposal call. Business plan for heritage, tourism, and education sub-project, 2002-03; CD-5261; Johannesburg Development Agency (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - #9456. Apartheid museum II: budget and reports, 1999-2002 (Box 37, Folder 1-3)
        - Constitution Hill, CD-5262; Johannesburg Development Agency (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - Constitution Hill-Johannesburg. Proposal Call. Business Plan for Hertiage, Tourism, and Education Sub-Project, 2002-03; CD-5261; Johannesburg Development Agency (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - #10834. Sabbatical of Graeme Simpson, 2002 (Box 169, Folder 18)
        Dublin cabinet file, Cab. 1, Dr. 4B 37/4/14
        Simpson, Graeme, 1959-
      - #10834. Director's sabbatical, 2000-2003 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - #11425. Constitution Hill, 2003 (Box 169, Folder 19)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/4/18
      - #11425. Constitution Hill: Phase III, developing an educational strategy, 2002-2004 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - #11948. Military veterans study tour, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - #11948. Military veterans study tour., 2003 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - #11948. Military veterans study tour, 2003 (Box 169, Folder 20)
        Dublin cabinet file 37/4/18/1
      - #13604. Six-month bridging grant, 2004-2005 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - #13604. Six-month bridging grant, 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - #14070. Re-integration projects for ex-combatants, 2004-2008 (Box 37, Folder 10-11)
      - #14071. Memory and memoralization project, 2005-2007 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - #16182. Project costs, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - #16182. Project costs, 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - #17380. Project support, 2008-2013 (Box 37, Folder 15)
        Due Process, Race and Intergroup Relations
      - Financial statements and annual reports, 2007-2009 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Charities Aid Foundation - Southern Africa, 2009-2011; Charities Aid Foundation
      - #18355. Social Advocacy Coalition for the Sustainability of Civil Society, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - #18355. Social advocacy coalition. Dem-Con., 2009-2011 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Children's Institute, 2002-2012; University of Cape Town. Children's Institute
      University of Cape Town. Children's Institute
      - #19000. Strenthening the organizational capacity of the Children's Institute, 2000, 2009-2010, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 19-20)
    - Community Law and Rural Development Centre (CLRD), 2009-2013; Community Law and Rural Development Centre
      Community Law and Rural Development Centre
      - #17954. Core support, 2009-2010, 2012-2013 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Constitutional Court Trust, 1994-2011
      Constitutional Court Trust
      - #7307 (#95-15). Salary support. Clerk's program, 1994-1996 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - #7307 (#95-15). Salary support. Research assistants program, 1995, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 23-24)
      - #7933. Supreme court (research clerks program), 1998-2000 (Box 169, Folder 21)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 4A, 37/3/3/2
      - #7933 (#99-138). Research clerks program. Supreme Court research assistants, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
      - #8019, #7307 (#95-15), #8090 (#00-95). PART 2, 1996-2001 (Box 38, Folder 3-5)
      - #8090 (#00-95). Bursary for Faizel Ismail, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        Ismail, Faizel
      - #8392. Ismail Mahomed Memorial Scholarship, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - #8392. Ismail Mahomed Memorial Scholarship. Scholarship fund in memory of Chief Justice Ismail Mahomed, 2002, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - #8818. Constitutional Court Library, 2000-2001, 2004 (Box 169, Folder 22)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 1, Dr. 4A 37/3/3/3
      - #8818. Constitutional Law, Public Law and Human Rights Law Library, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - #19440. Constitutional Court art collection preservation, 2010-2011 (Box 38, Folder 10)
        Public Arts
    - Contemporary African Music and Arts Archive, 2002-2005; Contemporary African Music and Arts
      Contemporary African Music and Arts
      University of Cape Town
      - #10562. Archive of Contemporary Music and Art in Africa, 2002, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - #10562. Contemporary African Music and Arts Archive, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Corruption Watch, 2013; Corruption Watch (South Africa)
      Corruption Watch (South Africa)
      - #21272. Incident management system and public education, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Democratic Nursing Organisation of South Africa (DENOSA), 2008-2012; Democratic Nursing Organisation of South Africa
      Democratic Nursing Organisation of South Africa
      - #17170. Building the capacity of DENOSA, 2008, 2010-2012 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - #17170. Building the capacity of DENOSA, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Development Resources Centre, 1996-2000; Development Resources Centre (South Africa) (Box 38)
      Development Resources Centre (South Africa)
      - #7535 (#97-62). Consultancy Services Department, 1996-2000 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - #7535 (#97-62). Consultancy services department, 1996-1999 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - District Six Museum Foundation, 2001-2004
      District Six Museum
      - #10038. Purchase of additional space, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - #10038. (Purchase of additional space) Sachs Futeran Building, 2001-2002 (Box 169, Folder 23)
        Dublin cabinet files, Cab. 1, Dr. 4B, 37/4/5/4
    - Durban Lesbian and Gay Community and Health Centre, 2002-2007
      - #13630. Core costs, 2005-2006 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - #13630. Core support, 2002-2007 (Box 38, Folder 19-20)
    - Durban University of Technology (DUT), 2007-2008; Durban University of Technology
      Durban University of Technology
      - #15569. Mid-level worker training capacity at DUT, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - #15569. Feasibility study (mid-level worker training capacity at DUT), 2007-2008 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - #16550. Undergraduate nurse training program, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Education and Training Unit, 2000-2004
      Education and Training Unit
      - #8758 (Organizational development website). #9999 (Updating paralegel manual), 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - #8758. Organizational development website, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - #9999. Updating para-legal manual, 2001-2003 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - #9999. Updating para-legal manual. HE (higher education), 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Equal Education in South Africa, 2007-2011; Equal Education (Nonprofit organisation)
      - #16826. Core support, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - #16826. Core support, 2007-2009 (Box 38, Folder 29-30)
      - #20058. Equal Education core support, 2011; University of Fort Hare (Box 38, Folder 31)
        University of Fort Hare
    - Fort Hare University, 2008-2010
      - #17609. Developing nursing scholarship, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - #17609. Developing nursing scholarship, 2008-2010 (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
    - Forum for the Empowerment of Women (FEW), 2004-2009; Forum for the Empowerment of Women
      - #13629. Core support, 2005-2006 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - #13629. Core support, 2004-2009 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
    - Forum of Nursing Deans of South Africa (FUNDISA), 2011-02; Forum of Nursing Deans of South Africa
      Forum of Nursing Deans of South Africa
      - #16793. Professionalizing FUNDISA, 2011-02 (Box 39, Folder 7)